cifrasfx.com.br 2017-05-04

# chords and tabs MegaChords.com

| 

|   
---  
  
| **Privacy Policy**  
---  
   
Computer Tracking and Cookies This site uses outside ad companies to display ads on this site. These ads may contain cookies. Although this site uses cookies in parts of this Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by ad companies, and this site does not access that information. Our web sites are not set up to track, collect or distribute personal information not entered by visitors. Our site logs do generate certain kinds of non-identifying site usage data, such as the number of hits and visits to our sites. This information is used for internal purposes by technical support staff to provide better services to the public and may also be provided to others, but again, the statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information. Mega Chords.com uses non-identifying cookies to provide easier site navigation and access to forms. You can still use the Mega Chords.Com sites if your browser is set to reject cookies. Our cookies do not generate personal data, do not read personal data from your machine and are never tied to anything that could be used to identify you.   
**Adsense**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google\s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).   
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/pdfs/NAI_principles.pdf).
